{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " Of which tree was Adam not to eat??",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Apple tree"
        },
        {
          "choice": " Fruit tree"
        },
        {
          "choice": " Tree of knowledge of good and evil"
        },
        {
          "choice": " Tree of Life"
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Tree of knowledge of good and evil ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " After disobeying, how did Adam and his wife cover themselves? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Coats of skins "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Fig leaves "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Jewish garments "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Modest apparel "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Fig leaves ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " What promise was made regarding the seed of the woman?",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " It would multiply as stars of sky "
        },
        {
          "choice": " It would multiply as sand of sea "
        },
        {
          "choice": " It would bruise the serpent's head "
        },
        {
          "choice": " All of the above "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " It would bruise the serpent's head ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who said, Am I my brother's keeper? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Abel "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Adam "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Cain "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Noah "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Cain ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " What son was born to replace Abel? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Cain "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Enoch "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Isaac "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Seth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Seth ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " What unusual thing happened to Enoch? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " God talked with him in the cool of the day "
        },
        {
          "choice": " God took him "
        },
        {
          "choice": " He died over 900 years old "
        },
        {
          "choice": " All of the above "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " God took him ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which man lived the longest? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Adam "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Enoch "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Lamech "
        },
        {
          "choice": " None of the above "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " None of the above ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who was a son of Noah? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " Enoch "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Japheth "
        },
        {
          "choice": " Lamech "
        },
        {
          "choice": " All of the above "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " Japheth ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " How many doors were in the Ark? ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " 1 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 2 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 3 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 7 "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " 1 ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    },
    {
      "question": " How many of each kind of unclean animal was Noah to bring into the Ark ",
      "time": "30000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": " 1 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 2 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 7 "
        },
        {
          "choice": " 14 "
        }
      ],
      "answer": " 2 ",
      "type": "epi_5"
    }
  ]
}